<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xml:lang="en">
  <generator uri="http://jekyllrb.com" version="3.8.6">Jekyll</generator>
  
  
  <link href="https://storiescovid.in/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" />
  <link href="https://storiescovid.in/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" hreflang="en" />
  <updated>2020-05-07T10:45:07+00:00</updated>
  <id>https://storiescovid.in//</id>

  
    <title type="html">COVID-19 Stories</title>
  

  
    <subtitle>Collection of real stories documenting the hopes &amp; harrows in the time of COVID-19 pandemic.</subtitle>
  

  
    <author>
        <name>Covid Stories</name>
      
      
    </author>
  

  
  
    <entry>
      
      <title type="html">Episode 1</title>
      
      
      <link href="https://storiescovid.in/2020/05/06/episode0/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Episode 1" />
      
      <published>2020-05-06T00:00:00+00:00</published>
      <updated>2020-05-06T00:00:00+00:00</updated>
      <id>https://storiescovid.in/2020/05/06/episode0</id>
      <content type="html" xml:base="https://storiescovid.in/2020/05/06/episode0/">&lt;h3&gt;Bugs Galore&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;!-- ![bug on the hand](https://drive.google.com/uc?export=view&amp;id=1Q_pMe9REiyVo68LYMmCiAsjwj5HrVSLH)  --&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don’t squash bugs. I blow them away or if they are particularly large, I make them amble on an A4 sheet and shake or flick them down from my 4th floor balcony. I like to think that they fell to their deaths and not just fly away to a different window, balcony or a tree, an act that I call these days “assisted suicide” - blame it on the TV series and movies.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;While packing enough chillis at the supermarket to last a few weeks, a small bug landed on my index finger. Instinctively I blew on it, but there it still was, round, small, impervious and unshaken, like our lockdown efforts that just blow up in our faces everyday. A realization set in slowly as I felt the settling perspiration on my lips and heard the breaths I drew - this is going to stay a while. — &lt;em&gt;Shantam Raj&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/images/ep1_2.jpg&quot; alt=&quot;bug on the hand&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</content>

      
      
      
      
      

      
        <author>
            <name>Covid Stories</name>
          
          
        </author>
      

      

      

      
        <summary type="html">Bugs Galore I don’t squash bugs. I blow them away or if they are particularly large, I make them amble on an A4 sheet and shake or flick them down from my 4th floor balcony. I like to think that they fell to their deaths and not just fly away to a different window, balcony or a tree, an act that I call these days “assisted suicide” - blame it on the TV series and movies. While packing enough chillis at the supermarket to last a few weeks, a small bug landed on my index finger. Instinctively I blew on it, but there it still was, round, small, impervious and unshaken, like our lockdown efforts that just blow up in our faces everyday. A realization set in slowly as I felt the settling perspiration on my lips and heard the breaths I drew - this is going to stay a while. — Shantam Raj</summary>
      

      
      
        
        <media:thumbnail xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/" url="https://storiescovid.in/images/ep1_2.jpg" />
      
    </entry>
  
  
</feed>
